powerretail.com.au 2018-04-03

# Privacy Policy - Power Retail

Privacy Policy

The Media Pad Pty Ltd, publisher of Power Retail, respects your privacy and is committed to complying with Australia’s National Privacy Principles and the standards of the Australian Privacy Act. Though we are not legally obligated to comply, we choose to do so in the best interests of our readers and sponsors. The following principles outline how we will collect, use, disclose, store and dispose of your personal information, in electronic form.

Collection and use of personal information

The Media Pad Pty Ltd will only store information that is of direct commercial relevance to the company. This information is collected for the purposes of providing the services purchased by the customer or communications requested by the customer. We will always use fair and lawful ways to collect personal information. Reasonable steps will be taken to ensure personal information is relevant, accurate and current. We will take reasonable steps to protect the personal information we hold from misuse and loss and from unauthorised access, modification or disclosure. Access to personal information is restricted to authorised The Media Pad Pty Ltd personnel only. Our system automatically captures the IP address of those who post comments. We reserve the right in circumstances such as attempts to mislead other users about a poster’s identity, to share that information. We will protect the anonymity of those who comment in good faith.

Passing of information to third parties

The Media Pad Pty Ltd will not pass any information of a sensitive, confidential or personal nature to a third party unless that subscriber consents to us doing so. The Media Pad Pty Ltd will occasionally distribute sponsored third party content to certain subscriber segments where it considers it relevant and of potential interest, and this content will be clearly marked as being created by a third party. Subscribers will always be given the option to opt out of receiving emails from The Media Pad Pty Ltd at any time. Access to Special Reports is complimentary via Power Retail, but the information you provide will be passed onto the third party sponsoring the Special Report as a condition of the free download. To the extent that the website contains links to sites operated by third parties and not related to The Media Pad Pty Ltd services, these linked websites are not controlled by The Media Pad Pty Ltd and we are not responsible for the privacy practices of these companies.

Queries or complaints

Any queries or complaints regarding this Privacy Policy or its implementation should be made to:

Privacy Officer  
The Media Pad Pty Ltd  
32 Ricketts Road,  
Mount Waverley, VIC 3149
